consumerhealthreview.org 2014-05-02

# Consumer Health Review: Privacy Statement

\- Consumerhealthreview.org is committed to protecting your privacy and developing technology that gives you the most powerful and safe online experience.  This Statement of Privacy applies to the Consumerhealthreview.org  web site and governs data collection and usage.  By using the Consumerhealthreview.org web site you consent to the data practices described in this statement. **General Site Use:** General use of our web-sites does not require any personally identifying information.  We do collect a limited amount of non-personally identifiable information that your browser makes available.  This information may include internet protocol (IP) address, browser type, browser version, browser language, and the date and time of your query on our site.  One or more cookies may also be used to help uniquely identify your browser should you return to our site at a later time.  This information is used for the purposes of enhancing our product and service offerings to you. **“Contact Us” Forms:** Some of our pages require that you enter personally identifiable information about yourself, and may include your name, email address, physical address, and/or phone number.  These pages allow you to contact Consumerhealthreview.org, and the information that you provide is used purely for the purposes of responding to your inquiries.  Under no circumstances will any of your information be provided, sold, rented, or otherwise be made available to any third parties without your express consent to do so, with one exception:  Should you place an order with us, your shipping address, but not billing address, will be provided to our carrier partner/s for the purposes of delivering your order to you. **Cookies:** The Consumerhealthreview.org web site uses “cookies” to help you personalize your online experience.  A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a web page server.  Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer.  Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you. You have the ability to accept or decline cookies.  Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer.  If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the Consumerhealthreview.org services or web sites you visit. **Information Sharing:** Consumerhealthreview.org does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties.  Consumerhealthreview.org may, from time to time, contact you on behalf of external business partners about a particular offering that may be of interest to you.  In those cases, your unique personally identifiable information (e-mail, name, address, telephone number) is not transferred to the third party.  In addition, Consumerhealthreview.org may share data with trusted partners to help us perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries.  All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to Consumerhealthreview.org, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information. Consumerhealthreview.org does not use or disclose sensitive personal information, such as race, religion, or political affiliations, without your explicit consent. Consumerhealthreview.org web sites will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on Consumerhealthreview.org or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of Consumerhealthreview.org; and, (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of Consumerhealthreview.org, or the public. To opt out of any future communication, email or otherwise please contact us atinfo@consumerhealthreview.org. **Our Commitment to  Security:** Consumerhealthreview.org secures your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. Consumerhealthreview.org secures the personally identifiable information you provide on computer servers in a controlled, secure environment, protected from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. When personal information (such as a credit card number) is transmitted to other Web sites, it is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol. **Changes to this Policy:** Consumerhealthreview.org will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect company and customer feedback. Western Herbal and Nutrition encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how Consumerhealthreview.org is protecting your information.
